<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
<title type="text">Nick Speal</title>
<generator uri="https://github.com/jekyll/jekyll">Jekyll</generator>
<link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="/feed.xml" />
<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="" />
<updated>2014-12-22T20:50:55-05:00</updated>
<id>/</id>
<author>
  <name>Nick Speal</name>
  <uri>/</uri>
  <email>Nick@Speal.ca</email>
</author>


<entry>
  <title type="html"><![CDATA[Christmas Card 2014]]></title>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="/Christmas-Card-2014/" />
  <id>/Christmas-Card-2014</id>
  <updated>2014-12-25T00:00:00-00:00</updated>
  <published>2014-12-25T00:00:00-05:00</published>
  
  <author>
    <name>Nick Speal</name>
    <uri></uri>
    <email>Nick@Speal.ca</email>
  </author>
  <content type="html">&lt;section id=&quot;table-of-contents&quot; class=&quot;toc&quot;&gt;
  &lt;header&gt;
    &lt;h3&gt;Contents&lt;/h3&gt;
  &lt;/header&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;drawer&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul id=&quot;markdown-toc&quot;&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#nick-speal-beng-14&quot;&gt;Nick Speal, B.Eng ‘14&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#mcgill-robotics&quot;&gt;McGill Robotics&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#road-trip&quot;&gt;Road Trip&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#a-new-life-in-berkeley-california&quot;&gt;A New Life in Berkeley, California&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;!-- /#table-of-contents --&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2014 was a big year for me. I reached big milestones in my robotics career: graduated from McGill, attended an &lt;a href=&quot;http://ncfrn.mcgill.ca/events/ncfrn-field-trials-montreal&quot;&gt;academic conference&lt;/a&gt;, built an autonomous underwater vehicle with McGill Robotics, and landed my first full-time job. I also got to spend more time than usual with family. We had a big Rooks family reunion in May in celebration of my grandparents’ 60th wedding anniversary and I was able to spend nearly a month in New York. This was in the middle of a huge trip that took all around North America, mostly in California. So much happened this year that I wanted to take this opportunity to share some of the highlights with my friends and family. I hope you enjoy it and consider sharing your highlights of the year too!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;/images/large/rooksfamily.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;Rooks Family Reunion&quot; src=&quot;/images/rooksfamily.jpg&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;nick-speal-beng-14&quot;&gt;Nick Speal, B.Eng ‘14&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Winter 2014 was the last semester of my Mechanical Engineering degree at McGill University in Montreal. In the past 5 years I made a lot of friends, learned a ton technically, and evolved as a person, so it was bittersweet to wrap up this chapter in my life. Still, I was very proud to have accomplished what I did – I was included on the Dean’s Honour List for academic achievement, and the Engineering Undergraduate Society presented me the Outstanding Leadership Award in recognition of how far we have come with McGill Robotics. In May, I walked across the stage to receive my diploma with my peers in line with me and my family in the audience, but I didn’t yet feel the relief of completion. I spent most of my time for the past 2 years with McGill Robotics, and we still had 2 months of hard work left before our robot would be ready for the competition.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;third&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;/images/large/gradfam.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/gradfam.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Graduation 2014&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;/images/large/gradfriends.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/gradfriends.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Graduation 2014&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;/images/large/gradfriendsthrow.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/gradfriendsthrow.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Graduation 2014&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;figcaption&gt;Click the images to enlarge&lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;mcgill-robotics&quot;&gt;McGill Robotics&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2013, McGill LunarEx Robotics built a mining robot for the moon, and competed at the NASA Lunabotics Mining Competition. We won 12th place out of 50 international teams and learned enough to be ready to return aiming for the podium. Unfortunately, interest in the competition was growing faster than NASA’s budget, so they decided to close their doors to international teams in order to accommodate 50 teams from the US. But 22 of us at McGill were itching to compete again!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;/images/lunarex.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;McGill LunarEx Robotics&quot; src=&quot;/images/lunarex.jpg&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We rebranded as McGill Robotics and found a new competition: and international competition in San Diego for autonomous underwater vehicles. The &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.robosub.org&quot;&gt;17th annual RoboSub Competition&lt;/a&gt; had a number of teams that had been improving their vehicles for many years, so we knew we had our work cut out for us in our very first year! I decided that the team would be better off in the long-run if we focused on building a strong core foundation of expertise, rather than trying to build a winning vehicle in our first year. This inspired the motto, Team Before Machine. &lt;a href=&quot;http://graphitepublications.com/team-building-with-mcgill-robotics/&quot;&gt;Graphite Publications&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;http://bullandbearmcgill.com/putting-the-team-before-the-machine-2/&quot;&gt;The Bull &amp;amp; Bear&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://publications.mcgill.ca/reporter/2014/07/mcgill-team-making-waves-at-robosub-competition/&quot;&gt;The McGill Reporter&lt;/a&gt; wrote articles about this strategy we took. Nearly 100 of us spent a full year working on this and a few other robots, learning so much in the process! In July, everything had finally come together, and my friend Mike and I drove the gear all the way across the country to San Diego for the big competition. It was a week of excitement, hard-work, socializing and learning from the other teams, and ultimately success!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We won 10th place overall, with 3rd place in Design and a special judges award for Best Branding and Business Development. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/media/set/?set=a.790759697622071.1073741832.451245104906867&amp;amp;type=3&quot; class=&quot;btn&quot;&gt;Competition Photo Album&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.mcgillrobotics.com&quot; class=&quot;btn&quot;&gt;McGill Robotics Website&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;/images/mcgillrobotics.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;McGill Robotics&quot; src=&quot;/images/mcgillrobotics.jpg&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;road-trip&quot;&gt;Road Trip&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In July, we had to get our robot, gear, and 25 people from Montreal to San Diego for the RoboSub competition. We didn’t want to ship the robot because it would have to leave much earlier and would leave too much faith in the hands of a shipping company. So Mike and I decided to drive, with the rest of the team joining us by airplane. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If we are Facebook friends, you can see the photo album &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/mike.king214/media_set?set=a.10202998127774211.1234920392&amp;amp;type=3&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. If not, you can follow along on &lt;a href=&quot;https://twitter.com/search?f=realtime&amp;amp;q=%23roadtorobosub&amp;amp;src=typd&quot;&gt;Twitter&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;/images/map.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;Road Trip Across the USA&quot; src=&quot;/images/map.jpg&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We picked a great 7-day route across the US, camping or staying with friends wherever possible. Our first stop was the cottage in Kingston, followed by a night in Oakville with my Aunt Allison and then a night out on the town in Chicago with some of Mike’s friends. In Nebraska we found a campsite off a beautiful lake, surrounded by hundreds of miles of corn fields and wind farms. The next stop was Boulder, Colorado, and Mike’s friend Tobin showed us beautiful views with a hike up a nearby mountain. From there, we had a stunning drive through the rockies and made it to Moab, Utah for sunset - a little too late for photos. So instead we woke up super early and caught the most amazing sunrise in Arches National Park before heading to the Grand Canyon. The next day we arrived in San Diego and headed straight for the beach to meet up with the team. We headed to Starbucks to talk business, and that kickstarted one last week of hard work. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;/images/roadtrip.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;Road Trip Across the USA&quot; src=&quot;/images/roadtrip.jpg&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After competition, the feeling of graduation finally kicked in. Bryan joined Mike and me in LA, and we started a tour of California. We went surfing with Julian on Manhattan Beach, then up to San Francisco, where Luc brought us to a party at Twitter’s HQ. John and Ally showed us a great time for a couple days in Lake Tahoe, and we spent a day in Yosemite before going back to SF for a tour of Google and another tech party at Dropbox. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;/images/la.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;Venice Beach&quot; src=&quot;/images/la.jpg&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/mike.king214/media_set?set=a.10203082245157093.1234920392&amp;amp;type=3&quot; class=&quot;btn&quot;&gt;View the full photo album&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Bryan could only come for a week, though, so Mike and I continued onwards. We hit LA and San Diego before coming back up the coast: taking our time driving up the iconic Pacific Coast Highway: Highway 1.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;One night camping in the renowned Big Sur, we met a big group from San Francisco. We kept in touch and have since become great friends now that I’ve moved to the city.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then Mike flew to New York to start real life, but I wasn’t ready to settle down. My friends Kate and Sam were doing a west-coast roadtrip too, so we agreed to meet up in Vancouver! On my way north I picked up some hitchhikers who showed me what might have been my favourite place on the trip: Mount Shasta. It’s a hippy town at the base of a beautiful mountain, and maybe it’s placebo or confirmation bias or something, but I could actually feel the positive energy in the air!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once I made it up to Vancouver, Kate, Sam, and I took the ferry to Vancouver Island and spent a couple days in Tofino. We had a blast!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;/images/tofino.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;Tofino&quot; src=&quot;/images/tofino.jpg&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.facebook.com/nickspeal/media_set?set=a.10154645422820226&amp;amp;type=1&quot; class=&quot;btn&quot;&gt;View the full photo album&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Back in Vancouver, Ed and his family were generous enough to put me up for some three weeks and I enjoyed the temporary stability of staying in one place with a bunch of my college friends in the same city. I’m especially grateful for the time I got to spend there with my Aunt and Uncle, Jan and Grant. We went on a big hike up to Lake Garabaldi, watched movies, and connected really well.
Eventually it was time to move on, so I aimed the car south and planned to spend a week in the woods in Washington and Oregon, 2 states that I didn’t get to see much of in my hurry to get to Vancouver. I was really looking forward to trying out the solitude, because the rest of the trip had always been with close friends. Unfortunately my timing could have been better and it was cold and rainy the whole time. I didn’t have the motivation to make a fire to cook for myself, so I was eating cold food and wasn’t particularly happy. Many people told me I had to check out the beautiful Crater Lake, but when I got there, it looked like this. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;/images/craterlake.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;Crater Lake&quot; src=&quot;/images/craterlake.jpg&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I resolved to just get south as quickly as I could to evade what seemed like the arrival of winter. Maybe it was a coincidence, but the instant I made it over the California border, things got better. The sun was out and I headed straight to the familiarity of Mount Shasta. I spent an afternoon in the park, drinking the freshest spring water you’ll ever taste, and playing frisbee with some people I met. They invited me to join them in their campsite so we hit the grocery store and drove straight up the mountain and took a hidden dirt road deep into the forest. It turns out these new friends of mine were traveling chefs! We made a big fire and ate like kings and I was very happy to be back in California.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After a magical few days in the Redwood forests north of San Francisco, I headed into the city to reconnect with the people I had met. Within hours of arriving, Katrina and Kavya invited me to an all-inclusive free concert featuring Aerosmith and Macklemore. It was surreal. I also got to check out an incredible music festival: Hardly Strictly Bluegrass. This free festival was 100% free of advertising and attracted 700,000 fans over the course of the weekend. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;figure class=&quot;half&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;/images/large/aerosmith.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/aerosmith.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Aerosmith&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;/images/large/johnbatiste.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/johnbatiste.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;John Batiste&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It was cheaper to fly home than to pay rent in San Francisco, so I took the opportunity to spend a month on the east coast. I got to spend more time in New York with the family than I had since 2010, and I also made it to Montreal, Boston, and Rhode Island visiting friends.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Determined to settle down, I finally moved out to San Francisco, but ended up popping up to Vancouver over American Thanksgiving, and dropped in on some friends in Seattle while I was in the neighbourhood. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;a-new-life-in-berkeley-california&quot;&gt;A New Life in Berkeley, California&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I got back to San Francisco, I was thrilled to receive a job offer from the top company I was interested in: 3D Robotics. 3DR is a 5-year-old startup with a mission “to help people see their world from above.” They make drones for aerial photography. I am starting in January as an Engineering Project Manager. They are working on an exciting new product, and it is my job to keep things moving along quickly. As issues come up, I’ll try to figure out what is going on and work with the relevant engineers to decide on a course of action. I love how this job will be dynamic and involve working with people. It’s a natural extension of what I’ve been doing at McGill Robotics and I can’t wait to get started. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;http://instagram.com/p/wZiuqyn0eD/?modal=true&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;3D Robotics&quot; src=&quot;/images/3dr.jpg&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Within 2 days of getting the job, I found an apartment nearby. It’s a beautiful home in the quiet town of Berkeley. I’ll be able to bike to work and hopefully will still hang out in the big city across the bay.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div align=&quot;center&quot;&gt;
  &lt;a href=&quot;/images/apartment.jpg&quot;&gt;&lt;img alt=&quot;3D Robotics&quot; src=&quot;/images/apartment.jpg&quot; width=&quot;100%&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In engineering school I’ve become fascinated with robotics and technology, and on my roadtrip I’ve fallen in love with the California lifestyle of helping your neighbours and being outdoors. I’m looking forward to a new routine in 2015, where I will hopefully have the best of both worlds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope you and yours have a very happy holiday season and will consider sharing an update on your year as well! All the best for 2015!&lt;/p&gt;


  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/Christmas-Card-2014/&quot;&gt;Christmas Card 2014&lt;/a&gt; was originally published by Nick Speal at &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;Nick Speal&lt;/a&gt; on December 25, 2014.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
</entry>


<entry>
  <title type="html"><![CDATA[Sample Post]]></title>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="/sample-post/" />
  <id>/sample-post</id>
  <updated>2013-05-31T00:00:00-00:00</updated>
  <published>2011-03-10T00:00:00-05:00</published>
  
  <author>
    <name>Nick Speal</name>
    <uri></uri>
    <email>Nick@Speal.ca</email>
  </author>
  <content type="html">&lt;section id=&quot;table-of-contents&quot; class=&quot;toc&quot;&gt;
  &lt;header&gt;
    &lt;h3&gt;Contents&lt;/h3&gt;
  &lt;/header&gt;
&lt;div id=&quot;drawer&quot;&gt;
&lt;ul id=&quot;markdown-toc&quot;&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#html-elements&quot;&gt;HTML Elements&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#heading-1&quot;&gt;Heading 1&lt;/a&gt;    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#heading-2&quot;&gt;Heading 2&lt;/a&gt;        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#heading-3&quot;&gt;Heading 3&lt;/a&gt;            &lt;ul&gt;
              &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#heading-4&quot;&gt;Heading 4&lt;/a&gt;                &lt;ul&gt;
                  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#heading-5&quot;&gt;Heading 5&lt;/a&gt;                    &lt;ul&gt;
                      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#heading-6&quot;&gt;Heading 6&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
                    &lt;/ul&gt;
                  &lt;/li&gt;
                &lt;/ul&gt;
              &lt;/li&gt;
            &lt;/ul&gt;
          &lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#body-text&quot;&gt;Body text&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#blockquotes&quot;&gt;Blockquotes&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#list-types&quot;&gt;List Types&lt;/a&gt;        &lt;ul&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#ordered-lists&quot;&gt;Ordered Lists&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
          &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#unordered-lists&quot;&gt;Unordered Lists&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
        &lt;/ul&gt;
      &lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#tables&quot;&gt;Tables&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#code-snippets&quot;&gt;Code Snippets&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#buttons&quot;&gt;Buttons&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

  &lt;/div&gt;
&lt;/section&gt;
&lt;!-- /#table-of-contents --&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;html-elements&quot;&gt;HTML Elements&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Below is just about everything you’ll need to style in the theme. Check the source code to see the many embedded elements within paragraphs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h1 id=&quot;heading-1&quot;&gt;Heading 1&lt;/h1&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;heading-2&quot;&gt;Heading 2&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;heading-3&quot;&gt;Heading 3&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;heading-4&quot;&gt;Heading 4&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;h5 id=&quot;heading-5&quot;&gt;Heading 5&lt;/h5&gt;

&lt;h6 id=&quot;heading-6&quot;&gt;Heading 6&lt;/h6&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;body-text&quot;&gt;Body text&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, test link adipiscing elit. &lt;strong&gt;This is strong&lt;/strong&gt;. Nullam dignissim convallis est. Quisque aliquam.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p class=&quot;image-pull-right&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/3953273590_704e3899d5_m.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Smithsonian Image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;This is emphasized&lt;/em&gt;. Donec faucibus. Nunc iaculis suscipit dui. 53 = 125. Water is H2O. Nam sit amet sem. Aliquam libero nisi, imperdiet at, tincidunt nec, gravida vehicula, nisl. The New York Times (That’s a citation). Underline.Maecenas ornare tortor. Donec sed tellus eget sapien fringilla nonummy. Mauris a ante. Suspendisse quam sem, consequat at, commodo vitae, feugiat in, nunc. Morbi imperdiet augue quis tellus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HTML and CSS are our tools. Mauris a ante. Suspendisse quam sem, consequat at, commodo vitae, feugiat in, nunc. Morbi imperdiet augue quis tellus. Praesent mattis, massa quis luctus fermentum, turpis mi volutpat justo, eu volutpat enim diam eget metus.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;blockquotes&quot;&gt;Blockquotes&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Lorem ipsum dolor sit amet, test link adipiscing elit. Nullam dignissim convallis est. Quisque aliquam.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;list-types&quot;&gt;List Types&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;ordered-lists&quot;&gt;Ordered Lists&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Item one
    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;sub item one&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;sub item two&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;sub item three&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Item two&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;h3 id=&quot;unordered-lists&quot;&gt;Unordered Lists&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Item one&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Item two&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Item three&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;tables&quot;&gt;Tables&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;table rules=&quot;groups&quot;&gt;
  &lt;thead&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Header1&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Header2&lt;/th&gt;
      &lt;th style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;Header3&lt;/th&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/thead&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;cell1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;cell2&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;cell3&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;cell4&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;cell5&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;cell6&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;tbody&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;cell1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;cell2&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;cell3&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;cell4&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;cell5&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;cell6&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tbody&gt;
  &lt;tfoot&gt;
    &lt;tr&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: left&quot;&gt;Foot1&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: center&quot;&gt;Foot2&lt;/td&gt;
      &lt;td style=&quot;text-align: right&quot;&gt;Foot3&lt;/td&gt;
    &lt;/tr&gt;
  &lt;/tfoot&gt;
&lt;/table&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;code-snippets&quot;&gt;Code Snippets&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;css&quot;&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nf&quot;&gt;#container&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;float&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;left&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;margin&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;m&quot;&gt;0&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;m&quot;&gt;-240px&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;m&quot;&gt;0&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;m&quot;&gt;0&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
  &lt;span class=&quot;k&quot;&gt;width&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&quot;m&quot;&gt;100&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;o&quot;&gt;%&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;;&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;buttons&quot;&gt;Buttons&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make any link standout more when applying the &lt;code&gt;.btn&lt;/code&gt; class.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#&quot; class=&quot;btn&quot;&gt;This is a button&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

  &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/sample-post/&quot;&gt;Sample Post&lt;/a&gt; was originally published by Nick Speal at &lt;a href=&quot;&quot;&gt;Nick Speal&lt;/a&gt; on March 10, 2011.&lt;/p&gt;</content>
</entry>

</feed>
